denschool.com 2013-06-02

# Homeschool Curriculum Software : Free Homeschooling Resources : Grade Report Card : Record Keeping Forms : Transcript : Planner : Online Homeschool Tracker

## Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

. To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

. To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

. To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

. To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

. To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and clicking on the applicable links.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act)

**Our Policy Regarding Children is:**

> **Information Collected**
> 
> We respect the privacy of children, and do not collect any more personal information than reasonably necessary to enable them to participate in the activities we offer at our Website.
> 
> With respect to our online information collection practices from children under 13 years of age: We collect the following types of personal information directly from children online:  
>  email address  
>  first and last name  
>  home or physical address including street name and name of a town  
>  an identifier such as a customer number held in a cookie
> 
> We collect the following types of information from children online and associate that information with one or more of the above identifiers:  
>  information about a child's hobbies  
>  information about a child's toys  
>  information about a child's parents or siblings
> 
> Please note that parents may consent to the above collection and use without necessarily consenting to the disclosure of personal information to third parties.
> 
> With respect to the collection by other organizations of personal information from children at our site, our policy is:  
>  We do not have any agreements with outside organizations to collect personal information at our site.
> 
> **Use and Sharing of Information**
> 
> The information we collect from children is used:  
>  for record keeping  
>  for marketing  
>  to enable them to participate in a chat room or bulletin board  
>  to respond to children.s specific requests to participate in activities such as:  
>  contests or sweepstakes  
>  subscription to an online newsletter  
>  voting in polls or otherwise expressing an opinion  
>  sending electronic greeting cards  
>  to tailor/customize the visitor.s experience at our site
> 
> With respect to sharing information:  
>  we do not share children.s personal information with anyone other than those who provide support for the internal operations of the Website and our agents (e.g., contractors who provide fulfillment services or technical support to the Website).  
>  We have received the following commitments for security of information from third parties with whom we share personal information
> 
> All third parties with whom we share information have agreed to maintain security and integrity of personal information
> 
> **Parental Review**
> 
> Parents can review the information that we have collected from their children online, prevent the further use or maintenance of such information, or direct the deletion of their children.s personal information by:  
>  emailing us at help@denschool.com  
>  visiting the following url: http://www.denschool.com

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.denschool.com/tos>

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [web site privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on September 30, 2009

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.denschool.com  
help@denschool.com
